sweettmakesthree.com 2017-08-17

# Privacy - Sweet T Makes Three

This post may contain affiliate links.

 **Privacy Policy for www.sweettmakesthree.com**  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@sweettmakesthree.com.  
At www.sweettmakesthree.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.sweettmakesthree.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.sweettmakesthree.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.sweettmakesthree.com does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.sweettmakesthree.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.sweettmakesthree.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Amazon  
Burst

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.sweettmakesthree.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

I am in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act.) I do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. My website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

_The owner of sweettmakesthree.com  is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com as well as other retail websites._

_I  do not promote products I do not own or would not buy myself. My goal is to provide you with shopping choices, product information and my own personal opinions or ideas for any given product or category. _ _You should always perform due diligence before buying goods or services online.  _
